BLACK SCREEN
It's beautiful here.
It was our aunt's. We used to come here as kids.
The Order uses it now as a safe house.
What's left of us at least.
Muggles think these things keep evil away.
But they're wrong.
I need to talk to the Goblin.
How are you?
Alive.
You probably don't remember that you...
That I showed you to your vault,
the first time you came to Gringotts.
Even amongst Goblins, you are famous Harry Potter.
You buried the elf?
Yes.
And brought me here.
You are...
...pretty unusual wizard.
How did you come by the sword?
It's complicated.
Why did Bellatrix Lestrange
think it should be in her vault at Gringotts?
It's complicated.
The sword presented itself to us, in moment of need.
We didn't steal it.
There is a sword in Madam lestrange's vault
identical to this one.
But it is a fake.
It was placed there this past summer.
And she never suspected it was a fake.
The replica is very convincing.
Only a goblin would recognize
that this is the true Sword of Gryffindor.
Who is the acquaintance?
A Hogwarts Professor.
As I understand that he's now Headmaster.
Snape.
He put a fake sword in Bellatrix's vault.
Why?
There are more than a few
curious things in the vaults at Gringotts.
And in Madam Lestrange's vault as well?
Perhaps.
I need to get into Gringotts.
Into one of the vaults.
It is impossible.
Alone, yes.
But with you, no.
- Why should I help you? - I have gold.
Lots of it.
I've no interest in gold.
Then what?
That.
That is my price.
Are you thinking there's a Horcrux in Bellatrix's vault?
Well, she was terrified when she thought we had been in there.
She kept asking you, what else was taken?
I bet you anything, there's Horcrux in there.
Another piece of his soul.
Let's find it, kill it,
and we are one step closer to killing him.
And what happens when we find it?
How're we supposed to destroy it,
now you're giving the sword to Griphook?
I'm still working on that part.
He's weak.
Who?
Mr. Ollivander.
I need to ask you a few questions.
Anything, m'boy. Anything!
Would you mind identifying this wand?
We need to know if it's safe to use.
Uhh... Walnut.
Dragon Heartstring.
12 and three quarter inches.
Unyie...
Unyielding.
This belonged to Bellatrix Lestrange.
Treat it carefully.
And this?
Hawthorn.
An unicorn hair.
10 inches.
Reasonably pliant.
This was the wand of Draco Malfoy.
Was?
Is it not still?
Well, perhaps not. If you won it from him.
I sense its allegiance has changed.
You talk about wands, as if they have feelings...
...can think!
The wand chooses the wizard, Mr. Potter.
That much has always been clear
to those of us who've studied wandlore.
And, what do you know about the Deathly Hallows?
It is rumored there are three.
The Elder Wand,
the Cloak of Invisibility,
to hide you from your enemies,
and the Resurrection Stone,
to bring back loved ones from the dead.
Together, they make one the Master of Death.
But few, truly believe that such objects exist.
Do you?
Do you believe they exist, sir?
I see no reason to put stock into an old wives' tale.
You're lying!
You know one exists.
You told him about it.
You told him about the Elder Wand...
and where he could go looking for it.
He tortured me.
Besides...
...I only conveyed rumors.
There's...
There's no telling whether he will find it.
He has found it, sir.
We'll let you rest.
He's after you, Mr. Potter.
If it's true what you say,
that he has the Elder Wand.
I'm afraid, you really don't stand a chance.
Well, I suppose I'll have to kill him before he finds me, then.
You're sure that's hers?
Positive.
How do I look?
Hideous.
You can give that to Hermione to hold. Alright, Griphook?
We're relying on you, Griphook.
If you get us past the guards into the vault...
The sword's yours.
Madam Lestrange.
Good morning.
Good morning? Good morning?
You're Bellatrix Lestrange, not some juvenile school girl!
Hey! Easy!
If she gives us away,
we must swear to use that sword to slit our own throats.
Understand?
No, he's right.
I speak stupid.
Okay. Let's do it.
I wish to enter my vault.
Identification?
I hardly think that would be necessary.
Madam Lestrange.
I don't like to be kept waiting.
I know.
They know she's an impostor.
They'd be warned.
Harry.
What do we do, Harry?
Madam Lestrange, would you mind presenting your wand?
And why should I do that?
It's the bank's policy!
I'm sure you understand, given current climate.
No! I most certainly do not understand!
I'm afraid, I must insist.
Imperio!
Very well, Madam Lestrange.
If you will follow me?
What is that, Griphook?
Griphook!
Aresto Momentum.
Well done, Hermione.
Oh no, you two're like you again.
The Thief's Downfall, washes away all enchantments.
Can be deadly.
You don't say.
Just out of interest, is there any other way out of here?
No.
What the devil are all you doing down here?
Thieves!
You gave up the...
- Imperio. - You!
That doesn't sound good.
Bloody hell!
That's an Ukrainian Ironbelly.
Here.
It's been trained to expect pain when it hears the noise.
That's barbaric!
Lumos.
Blimey!
Accio Horcrux.
It seems you're gonna try that one again, aren't you?
No kind of magic would work in here.
It's in here, Harry?
Can you feel anything?
That's it! Up there!
They have added the Gemino curse.
Everything you touch will multiply.
Give me the sword.
Stop moving!
Got it!
We had a deal, Griphook!
The cup for the sword!
I said I'll get you in,
I didn't say anything about getting you out.
Griphook!
Thieves!
Is that okay?
We've still got Bogrod.
That's unfortunate.
We can't just stand here, you got any idea?
You are the brilliant one.
I've got something, but it's mad!
Reducto.
Well, come on, then!
Relashio.
Keep moving!
Now what?
Reducto.
Hold on.
That was brilliant! Absolutely brilliant!
We're dropping!
- I say we jump! - When?
Now!
He knows.
You-Know-Who.
He knows we broke into Gringotts.
He knows what we took, and he knows we're hunting Horcruxes.
- How is it you know? - I saw him.
You let him in?
Harry, you can't do that!
Hermione, I can't always help it!
Well, maybe I can. I don't know!
Never mind! What happened?
Well, he's angry,
and scared too.
He knows, if we find and destroy
all the Horcruxes, we'll be able to kill him.
I reckon he'll stop at nothing
to make sure we don't find the rest.
And there's more.
One of them is at Hogwarts.
What?
You saw it?
I saw the castle,
and Rowena Ravenclaw.
It must have something to do with her.
We have to go there, now!
Well, we can't do that!
We've got to plan, we've got to figure it out!
Hermione, when have any of our plans ever actually worked?
We plan, we get there, all hell breaks loose.
He's right! One problem.
Snape's Headmaster now,
we can't just move from the front door!
Well, we'll go to Hogsmeade, to Honeydukes.
Take the secret passage in the cellar.
It's...
There's something wrong with him.
It's like, you know, in the past,
I've always been able to follow his thoughts.
And now everything just feels disconnected.
Maybe it's the Horcruxes.
Maybe he's growing weaker.
Maybe he's dying!
No!
No, it's...it's more like he's wounded.
If anything, he feels more dangerous.
- Right here. Come on! - Search everywhere.
Faster!
In here, Potter.
Did you look at him?
For a second I thought that was...
I know. Dumbledore!
Harry?
I can see you in this.
Bloody fools, what were you thinking, coming here?
Have you any idea how dangerous it is?
You're Aberforth, Dumbledore's brother.
It's you who I've been seeing in here.
You're the one who sent Dobby.
- Why've you left him? - He's dead.
Sorry to hear it. I liked that elf.
Who gave that to you?
The mirror?
Mundungus Fletcher, 'bout a year ago.
Dung had no right selling that to you.
- It belongs to... - Sirius...
Albus told me.
He also told me you'd likely be hacked off,
if you ever found that I had it.
But, ask yourself:
Where would you be if I didn't?
Do you have any others much?
From the Order?
The Order's finished.
You-Know-Who's won,
anyone who says otherwise is killing themselves.
We need to get into Hogwarts, tonight.
Dumbledore gave us a job to do.
Did he now...
Nice job? Easy?
We've been hunting Horcruxes.
And we think the last one's inside the castle.
But we'll need your help getting in.
Which job my brother has given you now, it's a suicide mission.
Do yourself a favor, boy. Go home!
Live a little longer.
Dumbledore trusted me to see this through.
What makes you think you can trust him?
What makes you think you
can believe anything my brother told you?
And in all the time you knew him...
did he ever mention my name?
Did he ever mentioned hers?
- Why should he... - Keep secrets.
You tell me?
- I trusted him. - That's a boy's answer.
A boy goes chasing Horcruxes on the
word of a man who wouldn't even tell him where to start.
You're lying!
Not just on me, that doesn't matter.
To yourself as well.
That's what a fool does.
You don't strike me as a fool, Harry Potter!
So, I'll ask you again, there must be a reason.
I'm not interested in what happened between you and your brother.
I don't care that you've given up.
I trusted the man I knew.
We need to get into the castle tonight.
You know what to do.
Where've you sent her?
You'll see.
Soon enough.
That's your sister, Ariana. Isn't it?
She died very young, didn't she?
My brother sacrificed many things, Mr. Potter.
On his journey to find power.
Including Ariana.
And she was devoted to him.
He gave her everything,
...but time.
Thank you, Mr. Dumbledore.
He did save our lives twice!
Kept an eye on us on that mirror.
That doesn't seem like someone who's given up!
She's coming back.
Who's that with her?
Neville!
- How you look... - Like hell, I reckon.
This is nothing.
Seamus is worse.
Hey, Ab!
We've got a couple more coming through.
Don't remember this on the Marauder's Map.
That's because it never existed till now.
The seven secret passages were sealed off,
before the start of the year.
This is the only way in or out, now.
The grounds are crawled with Death Eaters and Dementors.
How about Mr.Snape as Headmaster?
Hardly ever seen.
It's the Carrows who's watch out for.
Carrows?
Yeah. Brother and sister. Incharge of discipline.
They like punishment, the Carrows.
They did that to you?
Why?
Today's Dark Arts lesson was practicing the Cruciatus curse.
On first years.
I refused.
Hogwarts has changed.
Let's have a bit of fun, shall we?
Hey, listen up you lot!
I've for you a surprise.
No more Aberforth's cook gonna help.
We'll be surprised if we can digest that.
- Oh my! - Harry!
Get the word out to Remus and the others, that Harry is back.
Okay, okay!
Let's not kill him before You-Know-Who does.
Do you read? We've a new weather report.
Lightning has struck. I repeat: Lightning has struck.
What's the fun, Harry?
Okay.
There's something we need to find.
Something hidden here, in the castle.
And it may help us to defeat You-Know-Who.
- Alright, what is it? - We don't know.
- Where is it? - We don't know that either.
I realize there's not much to go on.
That's nothing to go on.
I think it has something to do with Ravenclaw.
It'll be small, easily concealed.
Anyone, any ideas?
Well, there's Rowena Ravenclaw's lost diadem.
Oh, bloody hell! Here we go!
Lost diadem of Ravenclaw?
Hasn't anyone heard of this?
It's quite famous.
Yes. But, Luna, it's lost.
For centuries. There's no person alive today who's seen it.
Excuse me, can someone tell me what bloody diadem is?
It's a sort of crown.
You know, like a tiara.
Harry!
Hi, there.
Six months she doesn't see me
and it's like I'm a frankie first-year.
I'm her brother!
She's got lots of them,
but she's got only one Harry.
Shut up, Seamus!
What is it, Ginny?
Snape knows... he knows that Harry was spotted in Hogsmeade.
Many of you are surely wondering,
why I have summoned you at this hour.
It's come to my attention, that earlier this evening...
Harry Potter was sighted in Hogsmeade.
Now...
should anyone...
student or staff attempt to aid Mr. Potter,
they will be punished in a manner
consistent with the severity of their transcription,
further more...
Any person found to have knowledge of these events...
who fails to come forward...
...will be treated as equally guilty.
Another...
If anyone in here has any knowledge of
Mr. Potter's movements this evening.
I invite them to step forward.
Now!
It seems, despite your exhaustive defensive strategies,
...you still have a bit of security problem, Headmaster.
I'm afraid it's quite extensive.
How dare you stand where he stood?
Tell them how it happened that night?
Tell them how you looked him in the eye...
A man who trusted you, and killed him.
Tell them!
Coward!!!
Harry.
Potter?
I know that many of you will want to fight.
Some of you may even think that to fight is wise.
But this is folly.
Give me Harry Potter.
Do this and none shall be harmed.
Give me Harry Potter, and I shall leave Hogwarts untouched.
Give me Harry Potter, and you will be rewarded.
You have one hour.
What're you waiting for? Someone grab him!
Students out of bed! Students out of bed!
Students in the corridor!
They're supposed to be out of bed,
you blithering idiot!
Sorry ma'am.
As it happens, Mr. Filch...
Your arrival is most opportune.
If you would, I would like you please,
to lead miss Parkinson and the rest of Slytherin house, from the hall.
Exactly where is it I'll be leading 'em to, ma'am?
The dungeons would do.
I presume you have a reason for returning, Potter.
What is it you need?
Time, Professor. As much as you can get me.
Do what you have to do.
I'll secure the castle.
Potter...
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you too, Professor.
Hold the fort, Neville.
Hurry up! Come on!
Harry!
Hermione and I've been thinking,
it doesn't matter if we find a Horcrux.
What do you mean?
Unless we can destroy it.
So, we were thinking...
Well, Ron was thinking, it was Ron's idea.
It's completely brilliant.
You destroyed Tom Riddle's diary with a Basilisk's fang, right?
Well, me and Hermione did remind where we might find one.
Okay.
Okay, but take this.
That way, you can find me when you get back.
Where're you going?
Ravenclaw common room, gotta start somewhere.
Harry!
Let me get this straight, Professor...
You're actually giving us permission to do this?
That is correct, Longbottom.
To blow it up! Boom!
Boom!
Wicked!
But how on earth are we gonna do that?
Why don't you confer with Mr. Finnigan?
As I recall, he has a particular proclivity for pyro-technics.
I can bring it down.
That's the spirit! Away, you go.
You do realize, of course,
we can't keep out You-Know-Who indefinitely.
That doesn't mean we can't delay him.
And his name is Voldemort.
Filius, you might as well use it.
He's come to try to kill you, either way!
Piertotum Locomotor.
Hogwarts is threatened.
Man the boundaries! Protect us.
Do your duty to our school.
I've always wanted to use that spell!
Protego Maxima
Fianto Duri
Repello Inimigotum
Protego Maxima
Fianto Duri
Repello...
Protego Maxima
Fianto Duri
Repello Inimigotum
Protego Maxima
Harry, wait!
I need to talk to you!
I'm a bit pre-occupied at the moment,Luna.
You don't know anything where you're going.
You're wasting your time!
Look, we'll talk later, okay, Luna?
- Harry? - Later.
Harry Potter, you listen to me right now!
Do you remember what Cho said about Rowena Ravenclaw's Diadem?
There is not a person alive who's seen it.
It's obvious, isn't it?
We have to talk to someone who's dead.
It's very impressive, isn't it?
If you've to find her, you'll find her down there.
- Aren't you coming? - No.
I think it's best if you two talk alone.
She's very shy.
You're the Grey Lady.
The ghost of Ravenclaw tower.
I do not answer to that name!
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It's Helena, isn't it?
Helena Ravenclaw, Rowena's daughter.
Are you a friend of Luna's?
Yes.
And she thought you might be able to help me.
You seek my mother's diadem?
Yes.
That's right.
Luna is kind.
Unlike so many of the others.
But she was wrong, I cannot help you!
Wait, please!
I want to destroy it!
They never learn.
Such a pity.
But, My Lord...
Shouldn't we wait?
Begin!
I thought you want to do it. Isn't it, Helena?
You want to destroy it?
Another swore to destroy it, many years ago.
A strange boy with a strange name.
Tom Riddle.
But he lied.
He's lied to many people.
I know what he's done! I know who he is!
He defiled it, with dark magic!
I can destroy it.
Once and for all.
But only if you tell me where he hid it?
You do know, where he hid it?
Don't you, Helena?
You just have to tell me.
Please!
Strange!
You remind me of him a bit.
It's here, in the castle.
In the place where everything is hidden.
If you have to ask...
....you will never know.
If you know...
...you need only ask.
Thank you!
Tell Professor McGonagall.
Remus and I will handle this side of the castle.
Yes, sir!
Hey Dean, on second thoughts,
tell Professor McGonagall
we might need one or two more wands this side.
It is the quality of one's
convictions that determine his success...
...not the number of followers.
Who said that?
Me.
You okay, Freddie?
Yeah.
Me too.
Harry talks in his sleep.
Do you know this?
No, of course, not!
Yeah? You and whose army?
You do it.
I can't.
Yes, you can!
Neville!
That went well.
Get inside! This way! Take cover! Take cover
Stupefy
Ginny, Neville! You alright?
Never better!
I feel like I can spit fire!
Have you seen Luna up here?
Luna?
I'm mad for her.
I think it's about time I told her
since we'll probably both be dead by dawn.
I know.
Bloody hell! We'll never find him on this.
Here he is!
- Just now... - Brilliant!
He just vanished.
I just now I saw it.
Maybe he's gone to the Room of Requirement.
It doesn't show up on the map, does it?
You said that last year.
That's right, I....I did.
Let's go.
Brilliant!
Come on!
Well, well...
What brings you here, Potter?
I could ask you the same.
You have something of mine.
I'd like it back.
What's wrong with the one you have?
It's my mother's.
It's powerful, but it's...
...not the same.
Doesn't quite understand me.
You know what I mean?
Why didn't you tell her?
Bellatrix?
You knew it was me.
You didn't say anything.
Come on, Draco!
Don't be a prat.
Do it!
Easy!
Expelliarmus.
Avada Kedavra.
Stupefy.
This is my girlfriend, you bloody gits!
Got it!
Goyle's set the bloody place on fire!
Come on! This way!
We can't leave them!
He's joking, right?
If we die for them, Harry, I'm gonna kill you!
Harry!
My Lord?
Avada Kedavra!
Come Nagini, I need to keep you safe.
It's the snake.
And she's the last one.
It's the last Horcrux.
Look inside him, Harry.
Find out where he is,
if you find him, we can find the snake.
And we can end this!
My Lord...
Might it be less...
I should not be more prudent to call off this attack.
Simply seek the boy.
Yourself.
I do not need to seek the boy...
before the night is out,
he will come to me! Do you understand?
Look at me!
How can you live with yourself, Lucius?
I don't know.
Go and find Severus.
Bring him to me.
I know where he is.
Come on!
No!
You have performed extra-ordinary
magic with this wand, My Lord,
in the last few hours alone.
No!
No! I am extra-ordinary. But the wand resists me.
There is no wand more powerful.
Ollivander himself has said it.
Tonight, when the boy comes.
It will not fail you, I am sure of it.
It answers to you, and you only.
Does it?
My Lord?
The wand, does it truly answer to me?
You're a clever man, Severus.
Surely you must know...
- ...where does its true loyalty lie? - With you.
Of course, My Lord.
The Elder Wand cannot serve me properly,
because I am not its true master.
The Elder Wand belongs to the wizard who killed its last owner.
You killed Dumbledore, Severus.
While you live, the Elder Wand cannot truly be mine.
You've been a good and faithful servant, Severus.
But only I can live forever.
My Lord...
Nagini, kill!
Take it.
Take it up, please!
Give me something! Quickly, a flask. Anything!
Take them to the Pensieve.
Look at me.
You really have your mother's eyes.
You've fought valiantly,
but in vain.
I do not wish this.
Every drop of magical blood spilled is a terrible waste.
I, therefore command my forces to retreat.
In their absence,
dispose your dead with dignity.
Harry Potter,
I now speak directly to you.
On this night,
you have allowed your friends to die for you,
rather than face me yourself.
There is no greater dishonor.
Join me in the Forbidden Forrest...
...and confront your fate.
If you do not do this,
I shall kill every last man,
woman and child
who tries to conceal you from me.
Where's everybody?
Harry?
Oh, come on! Don't be sad on it, she's passed.
There, she's gone.
Freak! Come here!
I'm gonna tell mommy! You're freak!
You're freak, Lily!
Come here!
She's jealous. She's ordinary and you're special.
That's mean, Severus.
Gryffindor!
- Hi, I'm James. - Hi, I'm Lily.
Just like your father.
Don't say a word against my father!
Servants and masters shall be reunited once more!
Severus.
No, don't kill me!
The prophecy did not refer to a woman.
It spoke about a boy born at the end of the July.
Yes, but he thinks it's her son!
He intends to hunt them down and to kill them.
Hide him... hide them all. I beg you!
What would you give me in exchange, Severus?
Anything.
Harry...
Harry, you were so loved.
So loved! Harry, mama loves you.
Dadda loves you.
Harry, be safe.
Be strong.
Avada Kedavra!
You said you would keep her safe.
Lily and James...
..put their faith in the wrong person, Severus.
Rather like you.
The boy survives.
He doesn't need protection, the Dark Lord has gone.
The Dark Lord will return.
And when he does, the boy will be in terrible danger!
He has her eyes.
If you truly loved her...
No one, can know.
I shall never reveal the best of you, Severus.
Your word?
Can you risk your life every day to protect the boy?
He possesses no measurable talent,
his arrogance rivals even that of his father
and he seems to relish in his fame.
Don't say a word against my father!
James Potter, lazy, arrogant.
- My father was a great man! - Your father was a swine!
Drink it up, it will contain
the curse to your hand, for the time being.
- It will spread, Albus. - How long?
Maybe a year.
Don't ignore me, Severus.
We both know Lord Voldemort
has ordered the Malfoy boy to murder me.
But should he fail, I should presume the Dark Lord will turn to you.
You must be the one to kill me, Severus.
It is the only way.
Only then, will the Dark Lord trust you completely.
It will come a time,
when Harry Potter, must be told something.
But you must wait, until Voldemort is at his most vulnerable.
Must be told what?
On the night, Lord Voldemort went to Godric's Hollow to kill Harry,
and Lily Potter cast herself between them.
The curse rebounded.
When that happens, a part of Voldemort's soul
latched itself onto the only living thing it could find.
Harry himself.
There's a reason Harry can speak with snakes.
There's a reason he can look into Lord Voldemort's mind.
A part of Voldemort lives inside him.
So, when the time comes, the boy must die?
Yes... yes. He must die.
You've kept him alive, so he can die at the proper moment?
You've been raising him like a pig for slaughter.
Don't tell me now, that you've grown to care for the boy.
Expecto Patronum.
Lily!
After all this time?
Always.
So, when the time comes,
the boy must die?
Yes.
He must die. And Voldemort himself must do it.
That is essential.
- Where've you been? - I thought you went to the forest.
I'm going there now.
Are you mad? No...
You can't give yourself up to him.
What is it, Harry?
What is it you know?
There's a reason I can hear them.
The Horcruxes.
I think I've known for a while.
And I think you have, too.
- I'll go with you. - No, kill the snake.
Kill the snake, and then it's just him!
I'm ready to die.
Resurrection Stone.
You've been so brave, sweetheart.
Why are you here? All of you.
We never left.
Does... Does it hurt?
Dying?
Quicker than falling asleep.
You're nearly there, son.
I'm sorry.
I never wanted any of you to die for me.
And, Remus, your son?
Others will tell him what his mother and father died for.
One day, he'll understand.
You'll stay with me?
Until the end.
And he won't be able to see you?
No.
We're here, you see.
Stay close to me.
Always.
No sign of him, My Lord.
I thought he would come.
Harry, no!
- What're yeh doin' here? - Quiet!
Harry Potter...
The Boy Who Lived...
come to die.
Avada Kedavra.
You can't help.
Harry, you wonderful boy.
You brave, brave man!
Let us walk.
Professor, what is that?
Something beyond either of our help.
A part of Voldemort sent here to die.
And exactly where are we?
I was going to ask you that.
Where would you say that we are?
Well, it looks like King's Cross station.
Only cleaner,
and without all the trains.
King's Cross, is that right?
This is, as they say, "your" party.
I expect you now realize that you and Voldemort
have been connected by something other than fate.
Since that night in Godric's Hollow, all those years ago.
So it's true then, sir.
A part of him lives within me, doesn't it?
Did.
It's been just destroyed
many moments ago by none other than Voldemort himself.
You, were the Horcrux he never meant to make, Harry.
- I have to go back, haven't I? - Oh, that's up to you.
- I've a choice? - Oh, yes!
We're in King's Cross, you say.
I think if you so decide,
you'll be able to board a train.
And where would it take me?
On.
Voldemort has the Elder Wand.
True.
And the snake's still alive?
Yes.
And I've nothing to kill it with?
Help will always be given at Hogwarts,
Harry. To those who ask for it.
I've always pride of myself on my ability to turn a phrase.
Words are, in my not so humble opinion,
are most inexhaustible source of magic.
Capable of inflicting injury and remedies.
But I would in this case, amend my original statement to this:
Help, will always be given at Hogwarts,
to those who deserve it.
Do not pity the dead, Harry.
Pity the living.
And above all, all those who live without love.
Professor, my mother's Patronus,
was a doe, wasn't it?
As the same as Professor Snape's.
It's curious, don't you think?
Actually, if I think about it, it doesn't seem curious at all!
I'll be going now, Harry.
Professor?
Is this all real?
Or is it just happening inside my head?
Of course it's happening inside your head, Harry.
Why should that mean, that it's not real?
Professor?
What should I do?
Professor!
My Lord, My Lord...
Are you hurt?
I don't need your help.
The boy... Is he dead?
Is he alive?
Draco, is he alive?
Dead.
Who is that?
Hagrid's carrying?
Neville, who is it?
Harry Potter... is dead!
No!
Silence!
Stupid girl!
Harry Potter... is dead!
From this day forth... you'll put your faith in me.
Harry Potter is dead!
And now it's the time to declare yourself.
Come forward and join us,
or die!
Draco!
Draco.
Come.
Well done, Draco.
Well done!
Well, I must say I'd hoped for better.
And who might you be, young man?
Neville Longbottom.
Well, Neville, I'm sure we can find a place for you in our rank.
I'd like to say something.
Well, Neville, I'm sure we'd
all be fascinated to hear what you have to say.
- Doesn't matter that Harry is gone. - Stand down, Neville!
People die everyday!
Friends, family.
Yeah.
We lost Harry tonight.
He's still with us.
In here.
So as Fred, Remus, Tonks...
All of them.
They didn't die in vain.
But you will.
Because you're wrong!
Harry's heart did beat for us.
For all of us!
It's not over!
Confringo.
Come on!
All remain into the castle.
We have to kill the snake.
Neville!
Not my daughter, you bitch!
Hey, you were right,
when you told Professor Snape that wand was failing you.
It will always fail.
I killed Snape!
But what if the wand never belonged to Snape?
What if its allegiance is always to someone else?
Oh, come on, Tom...
Let's finish this the way we started.
Together!
Die!
Harry!
Why didn't it work for him?
The Elder Wand?
It answered to somebody else.
When he killed Snape,
he thought the wand would become his.
But the thing is...
The wand never belonged to Snape.
It was Draco, who disarmed
Dumbledore that night in the Astronomy tower.
From that moment on and the wand answered him.
Until, the other night when I disarmed Draco.
At Malfoy Manor.
So, that means...
It's mine!
- What should we do with it? - We?
Just saying, that's the Elder Wand.
The most powerful wand in the world.
With that, he'd be invincible.
Together.
- Bag? - Yeah.
Jumper?
I'm gonna miss you.
Here they come.
Dad?
What if I am put in Slytherin?
Albus Severus Potter.
You were named after two Headmasters of Hogwarts.
One of them was a Slytherin.
And he was the bravest man I've ever known.
But just say if I am...
Then Slytherin house will have gained
a wonderful young wizard.
But listen, if it really means that much to you,
you can choose Gryffindor.
The Sorting Hat takes your choice into account.
- Really? - Really.
- Ready? - Ready.